Subtitties by TeddyCat!
Max!
Come on!
Don't keep the Sisters waiting.
This is Frey.
She's new here as well.
Can you read?
It's a giraffe. They were from Africa.
- You can read? - Yes.
"There are many robot servants, and they serve you all day.
If you live there, you never get sick or old."
- I'll take us there one day. - Really?
Yeah, I promise.
Frey and...
Max...
forever.
Max, have you been stealing things again?
It breaks my heart. Why do you do this?
So you can save up?
One day buy a ticket up to that place?
That place is not for you, or for me.
But it's not fair, Sister.
Why can't I go there?
Sometimes in life we don't understand...
why things are the way they are.
But I know one thing.
I know you are special.
You will do something very important one day.
Something you were born for.
My little Max.
Off to work, huh? Gotta get up early to work that line.
Make the world a better place.
That's real funny, I have a job.
Come on. You think I got money? Do I look like I have money?
Come on.
How about you? You got a little money?
Come on. What have you got in there? What have you got?
Oh, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Oh, it's 5 bucks. Hey, wait a minute, I got 5 bucks. I'm rich.
I can finally buy my ticket to Elysium.
All right.
Please form an orderly queue. Your bus has arrived.
Leave me alone!
Checked. Move on.
Your bags may be searched.
Good morning, officer.
Extensive criminal history. Multiple felonies. What's in the bag?
Hair products, mostly.
I'm just fucking with... Hey, hey, hey.
I'm just going to work. Nothing's in the fucking bag.
Come on, I...
I'm just going to work, man. Come on.
- Checked. - Nothing in there, is there?
Zero tolerance policy applies to all Citizens.
No shit.
You must report immediately to your parole officer. Thank you, Citizen.
No, thank you.
- Frey, fracture, Bed 2. - Just let us work, okay? Let us work.
Max?
Frey. I thought you were...
Been back for a while. I see things haven't changed.
- Ah, No, this wasn't even my fault. - Of course not.
- Let me have a look. Pretty bad break. - It isn't pleasant.
Yeah.
That's... That's great.
You still stealing cars?
No. God, no. I don't do any of that stupid shit anymore.
I work at Armadyne.
- On the line, working my way up. - They need you on the third floor.
Be right there.
So, you know, now that you're back...
Just a second, Max. Two seconds.
Dominica. Can you take over here?
Hey, listen. Now, you know, because you're back and everything...
Max, I'm so sorry. I have to go.
It's good to see you. Stay out of trouble.
I do.
Dr. Rodriguez, call the OR.
- Out of the way, sir. - Look, I-I get it.
I know... I know why you left the neighborhood. I understand.
But
If I was as smart as you, I would have left too. Have dinner with me. Just...
All right. Look, I'll settle for a coffee.
- No. - Oh, Jesus.
I gotta break my other arm to get attention?
- Stop. Stop. - Because I will do that.
My life is complicated, Max.
- My shift ends at 8 on Wednesday, okay? - Yeah. All right.
- Coffee. - Yeah, coffee. Right.
Get out of here.
Hello.
Uh...
Before we start, I'd just like to explain...
Max Da Costa. Violation of Penal Code 2219 today at Bus Stop 34B.
Yes, that's exactly what I wanted to talk to you about.
See, there was a misunderstanding.
Immediate extension of parole by farther eight months.
Wait, what? No, no, no. No, no. I can explain what happened.
Stop talking. Police officers noted violent and antisocial behavior.
We regretfully must extend parole.
Elevation in heart rate detected. Would you like a pill?
No. Thank you.
Personality matrix suggests a 78.3 percent chance of regression...
to old behavior patterns: Grand theft auto.
Assault with a deadly weapon. Resisting arrest.
- Would you like to talk to a human? - No, I am okay, thank you.
- Are you being sarcastic and/or abusive? - Negative.
It is a federal offense to abuse a parole officer.
Understood.
Safety is our priority.
- Hey. Da Costa. - No Weapons detected.
- You're late for your shift. - Yeah man, I had a little thing so...
Ohm, no, no, no, no. you can't work with that. You're out.
No, no, no, no. I'm good, man. I can work. I can work. This is-it's not, This comes off later today. I'm fine. - So you're good?
- Yeah, all right. - You know, You're lucky to have this job.
No Weapons detected. You are clear for entry.
the restroom more than once per shift. Please keep your Workstation tidy.
A tidy Workstation is an efficient Workstation.
Hey, Check it out, man. I think he likes you.
Think he got his face peel today? He looks good.
Attention. All workers must reach weekly quotas.
Please report any unsafe activity to your supervisor.
If we don't have a clear path to upside...
our investors are going to start losing a lot of confidence.
What do you think I've been doing down on Earth?
- You think I enjoy breathing this air? - No, of course...
I am doing everything possible to restore profitability to this company.
The company that I built.
Now, if you will excuse me...
I have to not speak to you people any longer. Thank you.
Closing 34.
Fire in 34.
Burn her ID!
We hacked three transponder codes, Spider.
Okay. Pull them up on-screen.
Codes have been accepted.
Fire up the shuttles!
We are going UP!
- Take a look at the garden. - We will. Thank you.
Yes, I understand...
My, how you've grown!
Are the children here?
Yes, with Dominica.
I have a present for you.
Go and get it with your mother.
It's next to the couch.
Ma'am, would you care for a refreshment?
Command: Cancel.
Sorry for disturbing you, ma'm.
We have a number of undocumented ships inbound.
Good afternoon, Defense Secretary Delacourt.
Three undocumented ships are approaching Elysium airspace.
Emergency orders six and seven are now in effect.
Protocol 22B-39 in progress.
Attention, incoming vessels.
You have made unauthorized entry into Elysium airspace.
Return to Earth or we will be forced to take immediate action.
You are in Violation of Elysium airspace.
The standard warning didn't work.
Fifteen thousand kilometers and Closing.
- What do you want us to do, ma'am? - Activate Kruger.
Ma'am, according to Executive Order 355...
we are unauthorized to use our assets on Earth.
I am authorizing you.
Yes, ma'am.
Agent 32 Alpha, we are sending a packet. Over.
Ten thousand kilometers and Closing.
Sending coordinates to asset.
Syncing target data.
Shoot them down.
Missiles away.
Two ships destroyed. Forty-six total casualties.
Impact in five...
- The last missile was a miss. - Ridiculous.
Only one made it.
Ma'm The ship has breached our atmosphere.
First undocumented ship just touched down.
I want everyone coming out of that vehicle apprehended.
Identification confirmed.
Scanning.
Reconstruction process initiated.
No.
We have 32 arrests, 13 casualties and two illegals still at large, ma'am.
You are under arrest under the 68-C Immigration Act.
- All illegals are now in custody, ma'am. - Yes.
Send them to Deportation. Get them off this habitat.
Secretary Delacourt, please report to President Patel immediately.
Secretary Delacourt, report to President Patel.
What up, man?
What happened?
- The police. - You okay?
Yeah. Don't worry about it.
- You didn't hear what I was gonna say. - All right. Go ahead. Go ahead.
Okay. You know the house of Los Zetas, up on the hill?
- Yeah, the one with all the guns. - Yeah. They have five cars. New ones.
It's gonna be three of us. Tomorrow at lunch.
- Lunch time. That's the plan? - Yeah.
- Jesus Christ. - What? You have a better plan?
Yeah. We just take one guy, go before the sun comes up.
You take the two fastest cars, torch the batteries on the other one so...
Fuck you, fuck you.
I got you. Oh, please man, you're the best. Give me one year.
- Just one year. - I'm not going back to prison, man.
One year, please.
Look at you. You used to be a legend, and now what?
The time is 5:50 a.m.
No weapons detected. You are clear for entry.
Closing 34.
Hey. You're holding up the line.
Attention. Workers may not visit the restroom more than once per shift.
- What have you done, Da Costa? - No, I'm just trying to reset.
- Oj, the pallet's pinched. - Yeah, it moved.
- Just go in there. - No. I mean...
Look, either you go in there right now or I'll find someone who will...
- ...and you can clean out your locker. - Come on.
No no. That's the deal, okay? In you go.
Let's go, people. Back to work.
Fuck.
No, no. No, no, no!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Hey, come on, you guys.
It's too late. It's too late, come on.
Come on.
Extraction!
They started the fight, Sister.
I just want to live there.
You see how beautiful it looks to us from here?
Yes.
Well...
Now look how beautiful we look from there.
Keep it.
This is yours now.
To never forget about where you come from.
What happened?
You have been exposed to a lethal dose of radiation.
You will experience catastrophic organ failure.
In five days' time, you will die.
What is going on? Why has production stopped?
- He's been exposed. - No. Don't breathe on me. Cover your mouth.
I'm sorry, sir.
Does his skin fall off or something?
I don't want to replace the bedding in there. Just get him out.
- Yes, sir. - Great. Thank you.
Mr. Carlyle, your shuttle is ready for departure.
Please sign this to receive medication.
Miporol, extremely potent, will keep you functioning normally until your death.
Please take one pill with each meal. Thank you for your service.
At 1500 hours yesterday, you shot down two shuttles, killing 46 civilians.
Your mandate is to deal with illegals quietly.
I am aware of that.
And then there's the use of this...
Fifteen human rights violations. Rapes. Kidnappings. Torture.
The man's been diagnosed with serious psychological issues.
We made it explicitly clear to you...
that we are no longer using sleeper agents.
Tell me something, President Patel.
Do you have children?
I am not the one being reviewed here.
Then I will assume you do not.
Perhaps if you did have children, then you would behave in a manner...
that is more conducive to the longevity of this habitat.
I understand that it is not the fashion to think and to act as I do.
I understand that perfectly.
But when they come for your house, for the house you built for your children...
and your children's children...
it won't be PR and campaign promises that keep them out. It will be me.
I've heard enough. This is your final warning.
Any further unauthorized actions, and you will be removed from office.
And let's discharge this Agent Kruger permanently.
All in favor?
Good. Effective immediately.
You want some beer?
You have been discharged from CCB.
Please return all weapons to the local embassy.
Fuck your politics, man! Fuck you!
Max.
What happened? Jesus. Let me help you.
Let's go in, come on.
Max, what happened? Jesus.
Max. What happened?
- I shouldn't have gone in, man. - Go in where?
Jesus.
I took a full dose, man.
I got a full dose.
They gave me Miporol, man.
They gave me fucking...
Miporol.
Five fucking days, man. I only got five days.
You have to take this.
- They can fix this shit on Elysium, man. - I know.
Max. Max, take the pill.
There you go.
To see Spider, you need money.
I'll give you everything I have, but it's not enough for a ticket.
He's gonna give me a ticket.
He's gonna give me a fucking ticket.
Frey, we've done everything we could to help your daughter.
I met with the board today and they recommend we send her home with you.
How can I work here and leave her at home?
It can happen any minute, Dr. Faizel.
I know. I know. If she has another seizure, of course bring her back to the ward.
Of course.
But until then, she's discharged.
This isn't Elysium. We can't just heal her.
Max.
It's been a while, my brother.
How's life at the factory?
I need to ask you a favor.
What? I-I can't hear you. What?
I need a ticket up there.
Ah...
Absolutely. Do you prefer aisle or window?
I'm being fucking serious, man.
Listen. I'm gonna come back. I'm gonna come back and work for you.
You know what?
This is priceless.
Do you have - do you have any idea how many idiots come in here...
saying the same kind of bullshit?
I got little kids coming in here every day.
I'd get the fuck out of here right now.
I did three years for you. After everything I did for you, you'll get me up there.
- Can you feel this? - Go ahead and shoot.
I got so much radiation in my body right now, you're probably getting sick yourself.
- You're really dying? - I'm fucking dying, motherfucker.
See this? It's over. Put the gun down. Put the gun down!
Put the gun down! Get out of here!
Okay?
But no one here had the balls!
Max.
All right, here we go.
This...
my friend...
This can be your ticket up there.
One last job for me, you earn your way up.
- What is it? - Take an Elysian asshole, right?
A billionaire.
He's down on Earth for some business.
He's-he's-he's here for whatever. We hijack him.
- Fuck that. - Okay, relax.
Forget his watch. Forget his ride. Forget all that shit.
This is what you take.
Organic information, right out of his head.
Now, I'm talking about bank codes, passwords, log-in data.
Access to billions.
All you have to do is plug into his brain...
download the data into yours with this baby...
and bring it to me.
This is crazy, Max. Come on.
Once we verify the data, I'll give you a one-way ride, all expenses paid.
Even throw in some snacks and a drink.
All you have to do is walk into a house and use the med bay...
and you're cured.
Sandro will do the surgery. You know him?
What the fuck? Jesus Christ.
I'm good.
Actually, you seem all weak a-a-a-and-and fucked up.
So you know what? I-I-I'll have them...
This is crazy. Let's get out of here, please. Listen to me.
- What the fuck am I gonna do? - I'll have them install...
this. A third-generation exo-suit.
We hook this into your nervous system, it'll make you as strong as a droid.
You're already under the knife, right?
Let's get out of here. Please.
I want a four-man team, but I pick them.
I'm sending my own data wrangler.
- Brain-to-brain data is real tough. - Okay.
But I'm taking Julio. He gets a ticket up there, same as me.
Yeah, sure. Okay. I'll go get the boys ready.
Wait.
It's gotta be John Carlyle.
The CEO of Armadyne Carlyle?
That's the mark.
Secretary Delacourt, Mr. Carlyle has arrived.
You are here to persuade me to renew our Armadyne contracts, yes?
Astute as always.
Come with me.
I'm not interested in your little ideas.
I'm interested in something much larger.
This habitat is dying.
There is a political sickness inside of it.
A tumor that needs to be removed.
You and your company are in need of revenue...
that is drying up.
So you built the torus.
Can you override the servers and place a new president in power?
A coup?
Are you suggesting a coup?
Is it possible?
I could write a reboot sequence and shut down the entire system.
And at that point...
Then that is what you will do.
And you will have your contract secured for the next 200 years.
Everything we need to protect our liberty.
All guaranteed, of course, by your new president.
You have work to do, Mr. Carlyle.
This is the guy.
- This is the guy? - This is him.
Sit down.
We're gonna out you a good one.
Play nice, Sandro. Play nice.
Let's get him an ID first.
Get the chief one of them identification codes.
Get that ready.
Arm up.
That'll merge with the DNA and you'll fit in like you were born there.
Now it's time for the real fun.
Okay. What we got?
Hey, man.
Yo. Is this gonna hurt?
Yeah, bitch, it's gonna hurt. It's gonna hurt good.
When we're done with you, you're gonna be a favela ninja.
Marianna, hey, bring down the bone saw.
- Bring the bone saw! - This ain't gonna kill me.
You're gonna be all right, my brother.
Max.
I'm here.
We got this, man. We got this.
Yeah.
Hey!
He's awake!
You can still jack off.
- How's everything going? - He's ready to kick ass.
What the fuck did you do to me?
Gave you a way out.
Damn.
What's up, partner? How's that suit working out for you, man?
That shit is tight.
Show me.
Hold that.
What's this, a family heirloom?
Wait for it.
Air-bursting ammunition. Designate your enemy...
and any round you fire will explode around them, five-meter kill radius.
And...
synced detonation rounds for this bad boy.
That'll work.
Move out.
Sir?
Shuttle is ready.
Do you read me?
Here's the deal. We'll wait outside the factory until we see his shuttle leave.
One of you puts an explosive round in it, goes to the crash site, gets the data.
Okay. Copy that.
Camera's live, boys. You getting this, Spider?
I got it. Let's go. Let's play ball.
- Move out of the way. - Coming through.
- You nervous? - No.
No?
I'm shitting my pants.
GO, go:
Acceleration to supersonic speeds in 15 seconds.
Come on, come OH, come on.
Ma'am, we have an Elysian citizen on Earth in danger.
Data coming up now.
Citizen identified. John Carlyle. N8321P...
I see you, motherfucker.
I have a situation here.
Miss Delacourt, how lovely to hear your voice.
There is a citizen carrying sensitive brain data out of the city right now.
- Some thieves are trying to hijack it. - What's in it?
That's classified.
You don't call a recently deactivated agent...
to retrieve classified fucking information, man.
The government doesn't know about this, do they?
I can ask for whatever I want, can't I?
Please brace for impact.
Please remain calm. You have sustained zero injuries.
Oh, that's a real comfort.
I got one condition. I do this, I get reinstated.
Fine. I've recommissioned two of your preferred agents...
completely confidentially, of course.
They should be at your position any second.
Send me the mission data.
Let's go, guys. Out of the cars.
Droids, there appears to be some type of wheeled vehicle with one...
Two occupants...
and they are armed and I'd like them dead.
Droid!
- No! - Identified. Max Da Costa.
Come on.
It's jammed, man!
Got it.
He's reloading!
- You all right? - We gotta go faster. I got the door.
Go, go! I got you covered!
Go, go, go, go!
Don't fucking move.
- Bring it! - There's another one.
Die, motherfucker!
Don't hit the mark!
No, no, no! No, no! He got hit, he got hit!
Citizen has sustained a cardiothoracic trauma.
Blood pressure is dropping.
It's not in the head. It's in the chest.
We're fucking good, man. Hold his head. Hold his head.
Plug this into you. Come on, get that shit in.
- Come on, baby. - It's in.
Yeah, yeah, we're syncing.
You have no idea what you're doing.
One minute to target, sir.
All right. All right, we're synced. Come on, baby, here we go.
It's gonna work. We got it. It's gonna work.
It's a data heist, ma'am. They're downloading now.
Guys, we got incoming.
Oh, fuck me.
Come on, guys, hurry up.
That's a Raven. That's military.
That's all right, we got this. Ninety-seven, 98.
- Hurry up! They're coming! - Almost there.
Oh, shit. Something must be corrupted.
- What the fuck? What does that mean? - Wait. Hold on. Hold on.
I can't read the data.
- It's scrambled. I can't read the data. - What?
Come on, guys, we gotta move!
- What the fuck does "scrambled" mean? - Fuck this.
No, no, no. We have to run it again! Run it another time, man!
Fucking get off me, man. I'm fucking bailing.
Please run it again.
- I can't. Get the fuck off me. - Let's get out of here.
Where the fuck are you going, Sandro?
Come on, Max.
Get out of there! Let's go!
We gotta go! Come on, Max. Come on.
Hey, boss. We got a runner.
Locked on.
Fire!
Shit, man.
That's what I'm talking about!
Fuck, man!
Targets moving south-southwest.
Move, Max. It's coming.
We got another one.
Okay.
This is wrong. This is all wrong, man.
Going into a holding pattern, sir.
Where do you think you're going?
Come on!
Fuck! Fucker!
Come on.
No!
No. No.
No.
Get up!
No!
We've got one assailant leaving on foot, ma'am.
They have the data. Repeat:
The thieves have the data. Apprehend the target at all costs.
Do not damage his brain.
Let's go! We got a runner, boys!
Citizen has suffered catastrophic blood loss leading to cardiac arrest.
Time of death: 1745.
Come on, where are you hiding? What's that?
It looks like a herd of pigs, boss.
Take us back to the crash site. See what they left behind.
Roger that.
Hey, boss. I think you'd better come look at this.
This is a record of what we picked up...
in transfer between Carlyle and the criminal, sir.
That's why she wants it so badly.
He's got the keys to the kingdom in his fucking head.
Now we just need to find him.
I'm gonna let the girls out.
Searching grids three through 11.
I'm authorizing a full containment order.
- All of Los Angeles? - The murderer is still out there.
Until we apprehend him, no one leaves the surface of that city.
What the...?
Max.
We can go home.
Am I better?
I'm gonna get the car, okay?
Be right back.
Frey....
Max.
Oh, my God. What happened to you?
- Shit. Let me get the medics. - No. No.
I can't go in there.
- Max, listen to me. You need a doctor. - I can't go in there. No, no, no.
People are looking for me. They'll kill me.
- I came for you. I need your help. - Max.
You've got to go through the system to get treatment.
Max.
Stay awake.
I wanna see the man.
Mommy's gonna help him, okay? Try and sleep.
Don't sleep.
Come on.
Stay awake.
Let's turn you over.
Max. Max, wait.
Thank you.
Who did this to you?
Oh, no, I got... I got hurt at work, and I had to...
I had to take a job from Spider to try to get up there and get healed.
It went bad.
- I'm in trouble. - Mommy?
Who's that man?
His name is Max. Mommy knew him when he was your age.
This is Matilda.
Hi.
You can go watch cartoons, okay? I'll be right there.
I didn't... I didn't know you had...
- I'm so sorry. I need to go. - Wait, Max. Wait.
- Don't leave. Wait. - I shouldn't have come here. I have to leave.
Max. She's dying. She's in the final stages of leukemia.
I told you my life was complicated.
I need you to help me. I have no idea how to do this.
- How to do what? - Get her to Elysium.
- I can't help her. I would... - Max.
- I would if I could. - What about this? Fake citizenship.
If you took her there, could you heal her with this?
It doesn't work that way. This is coded to me.
It's locked to my DNA.
These people who are looking for me...
You don't understand who these people are.
If they find me here, they will kill all of us.
The only thing I can do to help you is leave, I promise you.
- She's all I have. - I'm sorry.
You have bandages.
- What are you doing? - I don't want you to be sick.
- Do you wanna hear a story? - No...
There once was a meerkat who lived in the jungle.
He was hungry, but he was small.
So small. And the other big animals had all the food...
because they could reach the fruits.
So he made friends with a hippopotamus to...
Okay, stop.
It doesn't end well for the meerkat.
Yes, it does, because he can stand on the hippopotamus's back...
to get all the fruits that he wants.
What's in it for the hippo?
The hippo wants a friend.
I'm sorry.
Hey, boss.
I think we got him.
Land this fucking craft.
- Mommy, is everything okay? - It's okay, sweetie.
Clear.
It's okay, sweetie.
Afternoon.
Sorry to come bursting into your home.
I didn't mean to traumatize your young daughter.
Me and the boys here...
we're looking for a young gentleman...
who was in this very house a moment ago.
We're hoping you can tell us where he went.
No. I...
I don't know where he is.
I don't believe in committing violent acts in front of kids...
so I just need you to close your eyes, sweetheart.
It's okay, sweetie. It's okay.
I really need you to tell me.
Where is he? You remember now?
- Mommy. - Close your eyes.
Keep your fucking eyes closed. Keep your eyes closed.
Please, I don't know where he is.
He was wounded. I helped him and he left.
Please.
Do you fucking hate that? No loyalty nowadays, eh?
It's okay, sweetie.
And what's this here? This a hospital you running here? What's going on?
- She's sick. - She's sick?
She's sick? Let me have a look at her.
- Don't touch her. - See that? Protective instinct there, eh?
I said don't touch her!
I'm trying to get a word with your child. If you give me a second. Bring her. Come.
- Where are you taking us? - I've got something you want.
- It's okay. - Mommy.
It's okay, sweetie. It's okay.
Sit down. Shut up.
Stop.
Hey, hey, hey
No, no, no. Don't shoot him, don't shoot him.
Put the guns down. Let him come.
- You got something, didn't you? - What?
That's why they shut down the sky. Come on. What is it? Wire transfers?
Corporate intel? You gotta have something big.
I fucking got nothing, man.
It all got scrambled. Julio is dead. You owe me.
- Let's go fucking now! - We can't!
The flight system is jammed!
Nobody is going up there.
- Till when? - Till I don't fucking know.
- I gotta get up there, man. - Oh, everyone needs to get up there.
My guys are working to see if we have a hope in hell...
which I personally think we do not, of ever getting back online.
But for now...
let's just take a look at that head of yours.
- Get away from me, man. - Just look at me.
If they shut down the whole fucking sky for what's in your head...
maybe the key to opening it could be in there too, right?
Come on.
All right.
They will hunt you to the edge of the Earth for this.
What is it?
It's a reboot program for Elysium.
Whoever has this has the power to override their whole system.
Open the borders.
Make everyone a citizen of Elysium.
This can save your life.
We can save everyone.
When can I go?
They're trying to hack through the signal jam, but soon.
- Don't bullshit me. When can we go? - I don't know. Five days.
Fuck you. I don't have five days.
- I got hours. - My guys are working on it.
You're always working on it man. You don't... You can't get me up there.
I don't know even why do you even try sending people up there man. They just get fucking shot down.
Not with what's in your head! That's what I'm talking about.
We would control the system here. We would be in charge.
We can change the course of fucking history here.
Back up, then.
What I have in my head is worth a lot to them, right?
Don't do this.
If that falls into the wrong hands, they could shut us out for good.
Listen, man, I'm going up there right now.
Now, if you can find me and I'm healed, you can have all of this.
- But I'm not fucking dying. - This is wrong, Max. Don't do this.
Don't shoot him. Don't shoot him.
I always wanted a wife.
I just couldn't quite settle down, you know.
Too much temptation.
But you...
You make me ready to settle down.
You really make me wanna settle down, baby.
- Holy shit, sir. - Eh?
- You better take a look at this. - What? What is it?
Check this fucking oke.
Turn us around.
- Drakey? - Yes?
Open the door.
Stop right there!
You're gonna do exactly what I say or I'm gonna blow my fucking head off!
You can have everything in my head!
Just take me up there and get me in a med bay!
What I have is very valuable!
We can fix you up.
Put you in a med bay, sort all this kak up.
Let's go. We'll take you up there.
Weather's nice. Air's nice and clean.
Don't you fucking try anything.
Step aboard. Come meet the boys. Come, boet.
Don't be shy. They won't bite.
Let me introduce you. This is Drakey.
- This is Max. - How is it, butch?
Close up, Drakey.
Copy that.
Crowe, let's go.
Yes, ma'am. We apprehended the subject.
Open the skies, we're coming home.
Cancel the no-fly zone.
Yes, ma'am.
What? What?
What is that? What is that? Are we back?
- What the fuck is that? Are we back? - We're back online, Spider.
Frey.
I'm sorry. I'm gonna make this right.
We've got him.
All right. Where is he?
He's leaving Earth, heading to Elysium.
Manuel, Rico. Get weapons. Let's get up there.
Echo Leader 234 requesting landing in Sector 22.
Roger that, Echo Leader M-234. You are cleared for entry.
- I see you got the G-19. - Hey, back the fuck up. Back the fuck up.
- Or what? - I'll let it go.
I want what's in your head, boykie.
Come on. Come on.
Legs! Grab his legs!
Grab the grenade!
Hold on!
Get down!
- What do you want us to do? - I want everyone...
coming out of that vehicle apprehended by Homeland Security.
Evacuate everyone under Level 5 clearance out of the building now.
Matilda!
I warned you of this.
An unlicensed vehicle just crashed, potentially threatening the torus.
All because of your inability to act. Evacuate him.
- Get your hands off of me. - This is an act of war.
That puts the CCB under my control.
I'm sure you have a fundraiser to attend.
Let's go, sir.
Why are you not answering me?
Max.
- Take me out of here, Max! - Yeah. I'm trying!
Air quality reaching toxic levels.
Get me out of here.
It is recommended you exit the craft immediately.
- Run! - Come here, you fucker.
Two illegals heading northeast in Zone 3.
You deal with those two. I'll handle this poes.
Welcome to this spectacular property, sprawling over...
Error.
- No. - No citizen detected.
Please. She's sick. Help us. She's gone into a coma. Please.
Shouldn't we remove this thing?
Can't, till we get all the data. It's wired into him neurologically.
The data is intact, yes?
Data looks intact.
Warning.
We can still pull the data out of him, which will kill him.
Oh, that's fine. How long before you can download and turn the system online?
Not long, ma'am.
Keep everything in a restricted cloud. Lock down all access.
Starting prep right now.
And get these two out of here.
Roger that.
Crowe, you wanna go get the boss's chicks?
Yeah, boet.
Give them the runaround. Keep them busy.
Got him.
Let's go.
All right, 50 exabytes, buddy. You ready?
What are you taking out of him?
Hey. What are you doing to him?
What's gonna happen to him? Hey.
Rise and shine.
- Get up. - Max.
Max. Max!
Max!
Get in there.
Away.
Xa.
Boss got fucked up, eh?
Ate that fucking grenade, eh?
His brain is fine, but he's gonna be pissed when he wakes up, eh?
Remember the kak that happened in India when he lost his legs.
Kruger.
Hey, boss.
It's Crowe.
Where is he?
All right. We're all set.
Okay. Let's re-sedate him.
Got the needle prepped. Here, you wanna grab this and then...
Grab the needle! Grab the needle! Stick him with it!
- Where did they take the girls? - The armory.
- Where the fuck is that? - Level three.
Lethal radiation poisoning detected.
You idiot. Do you realize what you've done?
You crashed an unlicensed vehicle into a suburban area.
Your orders were to keep this covert.
Do you even remember what that means?
Have you completely lost your mind?
You're useless to me.
If the administration realized what we're doing...
they'd hang us both for treason.
Yes.
Yes, ma'am...
I'm listening.
I'm sorry that we crashed the vehicle and ruined someone's lawn.
But nobody is gonna hang us for treason.
We do the hanging.
Put your hand on it. Keep pressure on it.
Not so chirpy now, eh?
It's all right, boys. Elysium is about to get its first proper president.
She needs some medical attention.
I was gonna heal your daughter.
But now I will make sure that she is never healed.
Drakey, don't trust any of these politicians.
- You clear out this whole building. - Thank you, boss.
I'm gonna find that little gangster and I'm gonna take what's in his head.
This place is mine now.
You wanna come to my fucking house and play? Let's play.
I'm going to annihilate that little motherfucker.
I'm going to pulverize that little one.
Hey!
What the hell was that?
All members of CCB, please go to the nearest exit...
and proceed calmly to ground level.
No.
No more.
Citizen deceased.
Please exercise caution. Illegals detected in multiple locations.
Emergency systems are now online. Please follow indicated procedures.
Spider. Do you read me, Spider?
Max, where are you?
The thing in my head, it can make everyone a citizen here, right?
- Yeah. - You know how to get it out, right?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Okay, listen carefully.
Armory selected.
Set.
Turn me on.
Okay.
- Crowe, get rid of those two. - My pleasure, boss. My pleasure.
Where are you, boykie? Where are you?
How is it, girl?
- Let's play. - No.
- Come on. I'll be nice, I promise. - No, please.
- Come on. - Get off me.
- Want me to hurt the girl? - No.
- Then come here. - Please.
Oh, fuck!
You fucker!
The only way out of here is through me.
- Is she alive? - For now.
Stay behind me.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
I have a plan.
You hear that sound? That's the sound of me coming for you.
I will find you! I will hunt you down!
- Okay, Frey, we have to split up. - What?
Listen. You're gonna go to the surface, okay? Take this.
All right. Find a house. Get her to a med bay.
- It won't work. - Don't stop for anybody.
- She doesn't have an ID. It doesn't work. - It will this time. I know how to fix it.
- Surface selected. - Go.
- Come with me. - I'm right behind you.
- No. - I promise.
Okay. A mother and a daughter just went up in that elevator right there.
They're going to the surface, headed for a med bay.
Send one of your guys, make sure they get there, and we have our deal.
All right.
Right to a med bay, man.
- Go, go, go. - This way. Come on.
- Come on. This way. - Hurry up, man.
Emergency lockdown initiated.
Almost there. Almost there.
Pull it out! It's just a flesh wound, boet.
That's what I'm talking about.
- Fire has been detected. All affected... - Open the door. Open the door.
Areas will be shut down.
- Come on, come on. - I got it. Go, go, go.
Let's go.
Fucking door, come on. Go. You first, come on.
Emergency lockdown initiated.
- Please stand clear of all exits. - Come on.
Get up. Get up. Come on, let's go. Stand up.
Come on. Stand up. Stand up. Come on.
Come on. Stand up.
Hey
You little fucker.
I'm gonna take your fucking head off.
You should definitely stand up now!
Stay there.
Fuck.
Okay.
- You think you can get through me? - Come on, Max! Come on!
Come on.
Don't give up now. Get up. Come.
Come on, you've got more than that. I know you.
You look a little bit dizzy, eh?
Did I get you? Are you bleeding? You must get that looked at.
Eh, boykie?
You wanna heal that little girl?
You just need to come through me.
You almost had me.
Okay. Okay.
Okay. Come on, man. Let's go.
Okay. Let's go.
Get the door!
Come on.
All right. Let's do it.
All right.
What?
Max?
It's okay. I know.
There's no coming back from this.
No med bay can heal you.
All right. Give it to me.
Take it.
Okay. You just have to press that button.
Frey.
I'm gonna have to break my promise.
I can't make it back up there.
You remember what I said when we were kids?
Yes.
- I'll take us there one day. - Really?
Yeah, I promise.
You wouldn't believe what I'm looking at now.
Tell Matilda I really liked her story.
And I...
I figured out why the hippo did it.
Come on.
You first. Come on.
Everyone has one special thing, Max.
One thing that they are destined to do.
One thing they were born for.
Let go of me.
Come on.
Hey, Chiquita.
Hey-
Stand down, officers.
- Arrest him! - I cannot arrest a citizen of Elysium.
- What? - You did a great job.
Guess who Elysium belongs to now.
You see how beautiful it looks to us from here?
Now look how beautiful we look from there.
This is yours now.
To never forget about where you come from.
My little Max.
Subtitles by YTSMX. Translated by ChatGPT
Edited by TIKTOK/TrungLunReview